triplejack.com 2008-06-24

# Triplejack Poker

TRIPLEJACK.COM PRIVACY POLICY

**PRIVACY AND CONFIDENTIALITY**

TripleJack respects your privacy. Your privacy is important to us. Because we gather certain types of information, we feel it is important that you fully understand the terms and conditions under which we use the information we receive from you. We will never share your confidential personal information with anyone except as we discuss in this Privacy Policy. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your information will be treated as you make use of our products and services. Note that this policy may change from time to time, so please check back with us to view our updates. 

**PROTECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

TripleJack  will not collect personal information other than when it is willingly and knowingly provided to us by you. In certain instances, TripleJack may partner with service companies to ensure that you benefit from state of the art technology on our site. In order for these companies to provide services on our site, they may have access to certain personal information. This personal information will only be used by these companies to help us provide services to you such as personalized advertisements and will be kept confidential. 

**PERSONALIZING YOUR EXPERIENCE AND USE OF COOKIES**

We may personalize your experience by: providing recommendations to you about websites, and products that might be of interest to you. Notifying you about important changes to the TripleJack.com web site, new services available from TripleJack, our affiliates, and special offers we think you may find valuable. Cookies are pieces of information that are transferred to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. TripleJack may use cookies to see which areas of our site are popular, and which are not. By keeping track of things like trends and purchasing patterns, we are able to make improvements to our site and offer better service. We are also able to provide you with certain conveniences, such as remembering your preferences and helping you with your password. To utilize all TripleJack.com has to offer, you will need to make sure your browser is set up to accept all cookies. 

**LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES**

TripleJack.com may contain links to other sites. TripleJack is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. TripleJack does not share any of the individual personal information you provide TripleJack with the sites to which TripleJack.com links, although TripleJack may share aggregate data with such sites (such as how many people use our site. Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy. By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by TripleJack. Please check this page periodically for changes. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post any changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
